<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<resume>

	<Contact>
		<bullet>
			<text>819 Dufferin Ave, Winnipeg</text>
			<link></link>
			<image>address.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<text>+1 (204) 599 1138</text>
			<link></link>
			<image>phone.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<text>jimmy.vo.2410@gmail.com</text>
			<link></link>
			<image>email.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<text>jimmyvo2410.github.io</text>
			<link>https://jimmyvo2410.github.io/resume.html</link>
			<image>web.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<text>linkedin.com/in/jimmyvo2410</text>
			<link>https://www.linkedin.com/in/jimmyvo2410/</link>
			<image>linkedin.jpg</image>
		</bullet>	
		<bullet>
			<text>github.com/jimmyvo2410</text>
			<link>https://github.com/jimmyvo2410</link>
			<image>github.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
	</Contact>
	
	<summary>
	    <bullet>A Red River College(RRC) student with all As (GPA: 4.23)</bullet>
	    <bullet>A flexible, fast learner, and a supportive leader with the ability to categorize and automate software development process</bullet>
	    <bullet>Wide knowledge in various areas such as embedded systems, mobile platforms, database, web and application development with one-year experience as an automotive software engineer in a global company</bullet>
	    <bullet>Strong analytical, problem solving, decision making, organizational, time management and multi-tasking skills under high pressure (4 projects at the same time)</bullet>
	    <bullet>Strong interpersonal and communication skills achieved from multi-cultural workplace (Chinese and German)</bullet>
  	</summary>

	<experience>
		<bullet>
			<title>Peer Tutor</title>
			<date>January 2018 - Currently</date>
			<organization>Red River College</organization>
			<location>Winnipeg, MB, Canada</location>
			<descriptions>
				<topic> </topic>
				<description>Assisted students with programming skills (Web Development 1, Programming 2)</description>
				<description>Identified and filled out the students’ learning needs by reasoning and visualization</description>
			</descriptions>
			<image>RRC.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		
		<bullet>
			<title>Technology Camps Instructor</title>
			<date>May 1, 2018 - May 3, 2018</date>
			<organization>Red River College</organization>
			<location>Winnipeg, MB, Canada</location>
			<descriptions>
				<topic> </topic>				
				<description>Explained the technologies used in Web Development, Database. Networking and Web Security</description>
				<description>Led the discussion about ethical hacking</description>
				<description>Instructed the children to build up a simple website with database integrated, to find security holes and to enhance the site security</description>
			</descriptions>
			<image>RRC.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		
		<bullet>
			<title>Embedded Software Engineer</title>
			<date>May 2016 – July 2017</date>
			<organization>HELLA</organization>
			<location>Ho Chi Minh city, Vietnam</location>
			<descriptions>
				<topic> </topic>
				<description>Offered a promotion and invited by Chinese engineers to be a team leader on Radio Frequency Receiver technology</description>
				<description>Discussed with Chinese system engineers on the intermediate sleep/wakeup error that happened on some defective cars; convinced them to deal with the customer to accept my temporary solution to a bad hardware design existing from the first phase</description>
				<description>Supported a German system engineer to debug remotely on the NFC prototype</description>
				<description>Guided my team members remotely on the first demonstration of NFC in Germany</description>
			</descriptions>
			<image>hella.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
	</experience>	
	
	<education>
		<bullet>
			<degree>Business Information Technology Diploma</degree>
			<date>August 2017 - Current</date>
			<organization>Red River College</organization>
			<location>Winnipeg, MB, Canada</location>
			<major>Application Development, Database management, Web Development, Technology in Business</major>
			<image>RRC.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<degree>Electrical Engineering</degree>
			<date>August 2010 - March 2014</date>
			<organization>HCM University Of Technology</organization>
			<location>HCM, Vietnam</location>
			<major>Electrical, embedded system software and hardware</major>
			<image>HCMUT.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
	</education>

	<award>
		<bullet>
			<title>Applied Computer Education Department Award</title>
			<organization>Applied Computer Education Department, Red River College</organization>
			<date>June 7, 2018</date>
			<description>Awards of $1000 will be presented to students enrolled in an Applied Computer Education program.  Criteria include a letter of recommendation from an instructor, a portfolio of work of which they are proud, a grade report, as well as an essay that describes their experience in the program, their career aspirations, and include examples of class leadership.</description>
			<image>RRC.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<title>Great-West Life Award</title>
			<organization>Great-West Life</organization>
			<date>June 7, 2018</date>
			<description>An award of $2500 are available annually to students who will be entering their final year of the Business Information Technology program. Criteria include financial need, a strong academic record (minimum cumulative GPA of 3.00), as well as an essay or letter outlining volunteerism/community involvement. </description>
			<image>GreatWestLife.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<title>School of Business and Applied Arts Bursary</title>
			<organization>Red River College</organization>
			<date>February 16, 2018</date>
			<description>Red River College award endowment fund, established in part from contributions from the Province of Manitoba's Manitoba Scholarship and Bursary Initiative, or from funds established at The Winnipeg Foundation.</description>
			<image>RRC.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<title>Honor Roll Certificate - First Term</title>
			<organization>Applied Computer Education Department, Red River College</organization>
			<date>December 15, 2018</date>
			<description>First-term GPA: 4.45</description>
			<image>RRC.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
	</award>

	<skill>
		<area>
			<topic>Mobile Development</topic>
			<bullet>Java, XML and UI design (Android Studio)</bullet>
			<bullet>Deployed the applications to Google Play</bullet>
			<bullet>Analyzed, designed, and developed complex code bases, software systems, including API design techniques</bullet>
		</area>
		<area>
			<topic>Web Development and Database</topic>
			<bullet>HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP</bullet>
			<bullet>React, ThreeJS</bullet>
			<bullet>Web services and HTTP protocol</bullet>
			<bullet>Service worker, Web application</bullet>
			<bullet>XML, JSON, Oracle SQL, PhpMyAdmin, XAMPP, ZWAMP</bullet>		
			<bullet>Internet Security: SQL Injection, Cross Site Scripting</bullet>
		</area>
		<area>
			<topic>Application Development</topic>
			<bullet>C#, VBA, XML and UI design</bullet>
			<bullet>.NET application development (Visio Studio)</bullet>
			<bullet>Experience implementing modular, testable, and robust solutions</bullet>	
		</area>
		<area>
			<topic>Game Development</topic>
			<bullet>Hands on experience with C# script in Unity</bullet>
			<bullet>3D objects and common components such as physics and animations</bullet>
			<bullet>Deployed an VR game to Google Play</bullet>
		</area>
		<area>
			<topic>Financial Accounting</topic>
			<bullet>Understand business activities and financial accounting principles</bullet>
			<bullet>Hands on experience with Sage50</bullet>
		</area>
		<area>
			<topic>Embedded Automotive </topic>
			<bullet>Model base, manual code, code generation for all standard tools</bullet>
			<bullet>Module test, integration test, regression test</bullet>
			<bullet>CANoe, IAR, CppUTest, Tessy, Rhapsody, IBM DOORS</bullet>
			<bullet>Software Components: UDS Diagnostics, Active/passive Entry, UDS Diagnostics, RF receiver stack, NFC stack</bullet>
			<bullet>Basic Software: Diag Stack (DEH, IsoTP); System Stack (SysStateM, BleM, ucDrv, Gpt); Memory Stack (NvM); Io Stack (AdcDrv, DioDrv, SpiDrv, TauDrv)</bullet>
		</area>
		<area>
			<topic>Data Science</topic>
			<bullet>Kalman filter (KF, EKF), Gradient descent</bullet>
			<bullet>Computer vision (OpenCV)</bullet>
			<bullet>Data encryption, signal modulation (RF)</bullet>
		</area>
		<area>
			<topic>Embedded System</topic>
			<bullet>Control/Sensors: ultrasonic, EPPROM, DMA, gyroscope, accelerate-meter, magneto-meter, RF receivers, NFC, capacity touch sensor</bullet>
			<bullet>Protocol: UART, SPI, I2C, GPIO, SDIO, CAN, LIN</bullet>
		</area>
		<area>
			<topic>Embedded Software</topic>
			<bullet>C/C++ and assembly (Keil, IAR)</bullet>
			<bullet>MATLAB m-script, model base and C-file generation for embedded applications</bullet>
			<bullet>Experienced in independently designing, developing and testing of software module level API’s</bullet>
			<bullet>Developed configuration tools for different variants of an embedded platform</bullet>
		</area>
		<area>
			<topic>Embedded Hardware</topic>
			<bullet>Designed 2-layer PCB layout and schematic</bullet>
			<bullet>Proficiency in the use of soldering and measurement equipment such as oscilloscopes and logic analyzer</bullet>
		</area>
	</skill>
	
	<volunteer>
		<bullet>
			<title>Education Assistant</title>
			<date>March 2018 - Current</date>
			<organization>Red River College</organization>
			<location>Winnipeg, MB, Canada</location>
			<descriptions>
				<topic>Assisting the instructor in the course Network Computing 1</topic>
				<description>Indicated the issues, helped students with troubleshooting and explained network behaviors</description>
				<description>Helped students with Cisco Lab exercises in Open Lab periods</description>
			</descriptions>
			<image>RRC.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<title>Sessions helper</title>
			<date>June 5, 2018 - June 6, 2018</date>
			<organization>Prairie Developer Conference</organization>
			<location>Winnipeg, MB, Canada</location>
			<descriptions>
				<topic>Prairie Dev Con: A 2-day event provided a high-quality professional development opportunity locally, without the high costs of travel and accommodation typically associated with remote conferences</topic>
				<description>Answered questions at the welcome booth</description>
				<description>Ensured the machines worked properly during the presentations</description>
			</descriptions>
			<image>PrairieDevCon.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<title>Guest Speaker</title>
			<date>May 24, 2018</date>
			<organization>Red River College</organization>
			<location>Winnipeg, MB, Canada</location>
			<descriptions>
				<topic>The Campus tour: A day tour where international and ESL students come to see the college's facilities and the college lives.</topic>
				<description>Invited to come and discuss about the courses and the difficulties of international students at RRC</description>
				<description>Gave advise to ESL students about what they could do to prepare for the courses</description>
			</descriptions>
			<image>RRC.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<title>Session Helper</title>
			<date>April 12, 2018</date>
			<organization>DigiGirlz Day 2018</organization>
			<location>Microsoft, Winnipeg, MB, Canada</location>
			<descriptions>
				<topic>A great event hosted by Microsoft that RRC have had the fun and privilege to assist with for several years.</topic>
				<description>Robot Cars: Working with Adafruit Circuit Playground and some common household items, get an introduction to programming and electronics.</description>
				<description>Cognitive Thinking: Assist students through a series on non-technical activities to illustrate how they use critical and creative thinking.</description>
			</descriptions>
			<image>MS.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<title>Project Team Leader</title>
			<date>January 2018 – February 2018</date>
			<organization>Canadian Inventory Project</organization>
			<location>ACE Project Space, Red River College</location>
			<descriptions>
				<topic>An Android project sponsored by RRC to improve an inventory system in Canadian stores</topic>
				<description>Led the team on the software architecture and kept the software clean and maintainable</description>
				<description>Built a two-way peer review process</description>
				<description>Trained the team members on Android development and new technologies</description>
			</descriptions>
			<image>RRC.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<title>Workshop Assistant</title>
			<date>March 2018 - April 2018</date>
			<organization>Unity Workshops</organization>
			<location>New Media Manitoba</location>
			<descriptions>
				<topic>Series of workshops held by Dylan Fries biweekly to introduce Unity developers’ skill sets</topic>
				<description>Set up training materials</description>
				<description>Explored digital media world and many pieces of Unity</description>
			</descriptions>
			<image>NMM.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<title>Student Representative, Activity Facilitator</title>
			<date>February 20, 2018</date>
			<organization>RRC Open house 2018</organization>
			<location>Red River College</location>
			<descriptions>
				<topic>An event held by RRC to provide RRC’s program tour</topic>
				<description>Prepared LEGO Mindstorms demonstration</description>
				<description>Represented RRC’s students to answer CTV interview questions about LEGO Mindstorms</description>
				<description>Led the Coding-And-Networks-Games room, introducing high school students to basic concepts of programming</description>
			</descriptions>
			<image>RRC.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
		<bullet>
			<title>Note Taker</title>
			<date>February 1, 2018</date>
			<organization>DisruptED 2018</organization>
			<location>Red River College</location>
			<descriptions>
				<topic>An event sponsored by leading institutes (University of Manitoba, RRC) and the giants in the industry (DELL, INTEL, CISCO, IBM), to explore the future of work.</topic>
				<description>Hosted an unconference on how to bridge the digital divides</description>
				<description>Took notes in the unconference and reported to the event coordinator</description>
				<description>Discussed VR technology and start-up with young talents from high school in Winnipeg</description>
			</descriptions>
			<image>disrupted.jpg</image>
		</bullet>
	</volunteer>
</resume>
